underwoodfamilyfarms.com 2016-05-17

# Privacy Policy

The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Please read this notice. By using this site, you signify your agreement to our privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. 

**I. Information Which We Collect and the What We Do With the Collected Information**

We do not use tracking software that can identify you personally while you are visiting our web-site. We may perform statistical analyses of aggregate user behavior, but it is not based on personal identifying information. Any information we collect is used for its own internal purposes to improve the content of the web sites, to enhance user's experiences when visiting our site, to customize the content and/or layout of our pages and to provide the services required by an individual user. Any statistical analyses of user behavior will not be based on personal identifying information, but solely on aggregate information. We may share this aggregate information with advertisers, potential advertisers, or persons involved in product development or manufacture. 

**II. Use of Cookies**

Like many other commercial sites, our site may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our site is used. Cookies were designed to help a web site recognize a user's browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on a computer virus or capture your e-mail address. Our web site may use cookies to enhance your visit. They help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Cookies can securely keep track of selections, such as those selected in a "shopping cart." Our cookies may collect your domain name and track your selections through our web pages. We only use "cookies" to gather the information indicated in this policy and do not use cookies to gather personal identifying information about you without your consent. 

**III. Disclosure to Third Parties**

The owner and operator of underwoodfamilyfarms.com is Underwood Family Farms, Inc.(“Underwood Farms”). Underwood Farms will not sell, rent or trade any personal information about our online users to any third party without the user's permission, unless required by law. Underwood Farms will not collect personally identifiable information, such as your name and mailing address or e-mail address unless it is knowingly provided by the individual. If you choose not to voluntarily submit requested information, you may not be able to engage in certain activities -- e.g., making membership contributions or purchasing items from the shop -- for which personally identifiable information is needed.

We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses of users to third parties, such as advertisers, potential advertisers, or persons involved in product development or manufacture.

**IV. Accuracy of User Information**

Questions regarding our privacy policy, the accuracy of your personal information or the use of the information collected should be directed via e-mail to: [webmaster@underwoodfamilyfarms.com](mailto:webmaster@underwoodfamilyfarms.com)

You can also write us at: 

Underwood Family Farms  
PO Box 596  
Somis, CA 93066

These privacy policies are effective as of January 1, 2006. We reserve the right to change this policy as soon as it goes into effect.

**V. Security of Information**

The Underwood Farms website offers you the convenience of product purchases via credit card. Underwood Farms and our fulfillment agents, who support the Shop pages, utilize industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to safeguard credit card account information and personally identifying information from your computer to our servers. Our online financial transaction forms are stored and served from secure servers. Your peace of mind and the safeguarding of your credit card information are top priorities for us.

We use our best efforts to ensure the security of personal information submitted by users. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of information from your PC to our computers. Unfortunately, no electronic communication over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

Remember to sign off the underwoodfamilyfarms.com site and close your browser window when you are finished. This is to ensure that others cannot pose as you online. This is especially important if you are at a terminal that is accessible to others, such as the library, at school, at the workplace or at an internet café. 

**VI. Use of Materials**

The right to download and store or output the materials in our site is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of us is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on these sites may contact the webmaster: [webmaster@underwoodfamilyfarms.com](mailto:webmaster@underwoodfamilyfarms.com).
